So, where are your father and sister?
so, 你爸爸和你姐姐去哪儿了?
Mom, listen.
Mom, 听我说.
She interviewed me. But not for television.
她采访了我. 但是没上电视.
She's only on the radio.
她只在电台工作.
Who's on the radio?
谁在电台工作?
The reporter. She told me she's on the radio.
那名记者. 她告诉我她在电台工作.
And you know what?
还有 ,你知道吗?
She said she quit her job because she hated it.
她说她辞了她的工作, 因为她讨厌那份工作.
As a reporter?
当记者?
No. In an office.
No. 是在办公室里工作.
She had to stay in one room all the time.
她过去得呆在一间屋子里, 一整天.
And then, you won't believe this.
还有. 你绝对不会相信这个.
-She said she fed rats. -What?
-她说她养过老鼠. -What?
You know the rats they use in science?
你知道用来做实验的那种老鼠吗?
Yes.
Those rats. She fed them. She told me.
就是那些老鼠. 她养它们. 她告诉我的.
But Mom, isn't that so cool?
But Mom, 那不是很棒吗?
I want to do that.
我也想干那一行.
Feed rats?
养老鼠?
No. Be a reporter.
No. 当一名记者.
Mm. That's good, honey.
Mm. 很好, 宝贝.
Except I'm going to be on TV.
不过我要当电视台记者.